The Blues Are Back
Blues Brothers 2000 is a music, action, comedy film directed by John Landis.
Finally released from prison, Elwood Blues is once again enlisted by Sister Mary
Stigmata in her latest crusade to raise funds for a children's hospital.
Hitting the road to re-unite the band and win the big prize at the New Orleans
Battle of the Bands, Elwood is pursued cross-country by the cops.
Elwood Blues, played by Dan Aykroyd.
Mighty Mack McTeer, played by John Goodman.
Cab Chamberlain, played by Joe Morton.
Warden, played by Frank Oz.
Buster Blues, played by J. Evan Bonifant.
Malvern Gasperon, played by B.B. King.
Blues Brothers 2000 is a 1998 American musical action comedy film directed by John Landis from a screenplay written
by Landis and Dan Aykroyd, both of whom were also producers, and starring Aykroyd and John Goodman.
The film serves as a sequel to the 1980 film The Blues Brothers.
It also includes cameo appearances by various musicians.
The film was released on February 6, 1998, to mixed reviews from critics.
It grossed $32.1 million on a budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of prison, chicago,
illinois, orphanage, blues, half-brother.
The tone is lighthearted.